ahss.org 2006-09-26

# Privacy Policy

Disclaimer

The information on this site is provided "as is" without any warranties, express or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. Adventist Health System makes no representation or warranty that the information contained on this site will be timely or error-free. Adventist Health System has not reviewed all the sites that may be linked to its sites and does not endorse and is not responsible for the content of any off-site pages or any other sites linked to these sites. Your linking to such sites is at your own risk.

Privacy Policy

Thanks for visiting our web site. Adventist Health System appreciates your interest in our company and facilities. Your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel comfortable in visiting our site. Any personal information that you may give us, including your e-mail address, is used only in the following ways:

>   * In visiting our site, if you give us personal data in order to receive any type of information in return from us, we collect and store that data. That information is helpful to better design our site because we know the frequency of visits to the individual pages within our site.
>   * In visiting our site, if you view specific pages or download information from specific pages, we track visits to those pages in order to measure the number of visitors to our web site. That information is helpful to better design our site because we know which pages within our site are frequented. However, we do not automatically collect your personal e-mail address simply because you visit our site. All we know, based on the information that we collect, is the number of times on a date that a particular page was visited.
>   * We may share aggregate Êdemographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify you or any other visitor to our web site. If we partner in the future with a third party to provide services, when you sign up for these services we will share names and other contact information that is necessary for our partner to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use your personally-identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
>
